(Howard(in Stephen Hawking voice):)You're right.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Who am I kidding?
You should've seen me
when I was young, Sheldon.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)The fellas used to line up
and bring me boxes of candy.
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Why did I eat it all?
(Mrs Wolowitz(off):)Would you hold me?
(Sheldon:)Oh. No, you know,
I'm not really the holding kind of...
(Sheldon:)Oh!
(Howard:)Oh, guys, I just remembered.
l got you some Hawking souvenirs.
(Leonard:)What are these?
(Howard:)Gears and springs
from his wheelchair.
(Howard:)Pretty cool, huh?
(Raj:)Wow. That's amazing.
(Howard:)Yeah, I made an adjustment
on the motor drive...
(Howard:)...and when I was putting it
back together...
...l could not for the life of me
figure out where they went.
l did it.
(Sheldon:)Had to go to three clothing stores...
(Sheldon:)...but we finally found a dress
that could envelop your mother.